A Guide to the Lucille P. Markey Charitable Trust records FA017
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Scholars and Visiting Fellows, 1983-1998; 1
  - Scholar Applicants, 1983-1998; 1
    - Denied Applicants, 1984-1990; B
      - Joshi, Shantaram S. - Application 840054 (Reel 27, Frame 1179)
      - Nagarkatti, Prakash S. - Application 840055 (Reel 27, Frame 1215)
      - Eisen, Judith S. - Application 840056 (Reel 27, Frame 1248)
      - Presson, Joelle C. - Application 840057 (Reel 27, Frame 1279)
      - Buckley, Kathleen M. - Application 840058 (Reel 27, Frame 1308)
      - Mroczkowski, Barbara - Application 840059 (Reel 27, Frame 1340)
      - Runge, Val M. - Application 840060 (Reel 27, Frame 1374)
      - Murray, John J. - Application 840061 (Reel 27, Frame 1413)
      - Salas, Pedro J. I. - Application 840062 (Reel 28, Frame 1)
      - Carp, Jonathan S. - Application 840063 (Reel 28, Frame 39)
      - Hillard, Cecilia J. - Application 840064 (Reel 28, Frame 69)
      - Kenney, W. Larry - Application 840065 (Reel 28, Frame 101)
      - Leff, Todd - Application 840066 (Reel 28, Frame 132)
      - Nagy, Ferenc - Application 840067 (Reel 28, Frame 165)
      - Sciandra, James J. - Application 840068 (Reel 28, Frame 194)
      - Brotherton, Timothy W. - Application 840069 (Reel 28, Frame 230)
      - Birnbaum, Morris - Application 840070 (Reel 28, Frame 260)
      - Rachow, John W. - Application 840071 (Reel 28, Frame 291)
      - Beehler, Connie J. - Application 840072 (Reel 28, Frame 324)
      - Nicosia, Roberto F. - Application 840073 (Reel 28, Frame 360)
      - Hempleman, Steven C. - Application 840074 (Reel 28, Frame 396)
      - Kessel, Ann T. - Application 840075 (Reel 28, Frame 431)
      - Hruszkewycz, Andrew - Application 840076 (Reel 28, Frame 458)
      - Adler, Mark J. - Application 840077 (Reel 28, Frame 495)
      - Fox, Niles - Application 840078 (Reel 28, Frame 520)
      - Sterling, Kenneth M. - Application 840079 (Reel 28, Frame 556)
      - Handelsman, Leonard - Application 840080 (Reel 28, Frame 587)
      - Alderman, Jeffrey A. - Application 840081 (Reel 28, Frame 613)
      - Harpaz, Noam - Application 840082 (Reel 28, Frame 638)
      - Kwon, Byoung Se - Application 840083 (Reel 28, Frame 666)
      - Joyce, Gerald F. - Application 840084 (Reel 28, Frame 707)
      - Bestwick, Richard K. - Application 840085 (Reel 28, Frame 736)
      - Ellsworth, Mary L. - Application 840086 (Reel 28, Frame 774)
      - Shaw, George M. - Application 840087 (Reel 28, Frame 805)
      - Bregman, Barbara S. - Application 840088 (Reel 28, Frame 862)
      - Hamlyn, John M. - Application 840089 (Reel 28, Frame 898)
      - Marban, Eduardo - Application 840091 (Reel 28, Frame 937)
      - Lo, Matthew M. S. - Application 840092 (Reel 28, Frame 977)
      - Federspiel, William J. - Application 840093 (Reel 28, Frame 1009)
      - Conrad, Chester H. - Application 840094 (Reel 28, Frame 1037)
      - Sypek, Joseph P. - Application 840095 (Reel 28, Frame 1070)
      - Dorner, Andrew J. - Application 840096 (Reel 28, Frame 1102)
      - Theoharides, Theoharis C. - Application 840097 (Reel 28, Frame 1134)
      - Stern, David F. - Application 840098 (Reel 28, Frame 1169)
      - Lenardo, Michael J. - Application 840099 (Reel 28, Frame 1198)
      - Pfeffer, Suzanne R. - Application 840101 (Reel 29, Frame 1)
      - Arsenakis, Minas - Application 840102 (Reel 29, Frame 27)
      - Smalheiser, Neil - Application 840103 (Reel 29, Frame 58)
      - Buxton, Denis B. - Application 840104 (Reel 29, Frame 88)
      - Weiner, Francis R. - Application 840105 (Reel 29, Frame 112)
      - Darrow, Timothy L. - Application 840106 (Reel 29, Frame 143)
      - Lebovitz, Russell M. - Application 840107 (Reel 29, Frame 174)
      - Farrell, Michael P. - Application 840108 (Reel 29, Frame 206)
      - Dunham, Bernadette M. - Application 840109 (Reel 29, Frame 236)
      - Korfhagen, Thomas R. - Application 840110 (Reel 29, Frame 264)
      - Coombs, Sheryl L. - Application 840111 (Reel 29, Frame 299)
      - Gawryl, Maria S. - Application 840112 (Reel 29, Frame 332)
      - Ammons, W. Steve - Application 840113 (Reel 29, Frame 370)
      - Geppart, Thomas - Application 840114 (Reel 29, Frame 399)
      - Davidson, Anne - Application 840115 (Reel 29, Frame 431)
      - Klein, Jon B. - Application 840116 (Reel 29, Frame 464)
      - Izant, Jonathan G. - Application 840117 (Reel 29, Frame 494)
      - Garber, David W. - Application 840118 (Reel 29, Frame 518)
      - Spivey, William H. - Application 840119 (Reel 29, Frame 548)
      - Grisham, Matthew B. - Application 840120 (Reel 29, Frame 580)
      - Douthwaite, Stephen R. - Application 840121 (Reel 29, Frame 609)
      - Lockette, Warren - Application 840123 (Reel 29, Frame 640)
      - Schleifer, Leonard S. - Application 840124 (Reel 29, Frame 670)
      - Been, Michael D. - Application 840125 (Reel 29, Frame 699)
      - Zubenko, George S. - Application 840126 (Reel 29, Frame 725)
      - Wolkowicz, Paul E. - Application 840127 (Reel 29, Frame 770)
      - Purkey, John A. - Application 840128 (Reel 29, Frame 802)
      - Grigonis, Antony M. - Application 840129 (Reel 29, Frame 847)
      - Clarke, Stephen H. - Application 840131 (Reel 29, Frame 922)
      - Baeker, Thomas R. - Application 840132 (Reel 29, Frame 951)
      - Ianuzzi, Michael C. - Application 840133 (Reel 29, Frame 983)
      - Warren, Stephen T. - Application 840134 (Reel 29, Frame 1026)
      - Taylor, Douglas D. - Application 840136 (Reel 29, Frame 1059)
      - Laughon, Allen S. - Application 840137 (Reel 29, Frame 1084)
      - Price, Ray M. - Application 840138 (Reel 29, Frame 1110)
      - Troy, John B. - Application 840139 (Reel 29, Frame 1143)
      - Allen, Jonathan C. - Application 840140 (Reel 29, Frame 1177)
      - Pierce, William M., Jr. - Application 840141 (Reel 30, Frame 1)
      - Libertin, Claudia R. - Application 840142 (Reel 30, Frame 26)
      - Elder, James T. - Application 840144 (Reel 30, Frame 51)
      - Verselis, Vvtautas K. - Application 840145 (Reel 30, Frame 87)
      - Osborne, Timothy F. - Application 840146 (Reel 30, Frame 116)
      - Lalor, Thomas M. - Application 840147 (Reel 30, Frame 146)
      - Lynch, Joseph J. - Application 840148 (Reel 30, Frame 172)
      - Foster, Carol M. - Application 840149 (Reel 30, Frame 207)
      - Hiserodt, John C. - Application 840150 (Reel 30, Frame 238)
      - Lowy, R. Joel - Application 840151 (Reel 30, Frame 273)
      - Robbins, David J. - Application 840152 (Reel 30, Frame 306)
      - Genain, Claude P. - Application 840153 (Reel 30, Frame 336)
      - Nielsen, Laust H. - Application 840154 (Reel 30, Frame 385)
      - White, Morris F. - Application 840155 (Reel 30, Frame 417)
      - Grundfest, Warren S. - Application 840156 (Reel 30, Frame 458)
      - Eigler, Neal L. - Application 840157 (Reel 30, Frame 498)
      - Kipps, Thomas J. - Application 840158 (Reel 30, Frame 537)
      - Molony, Donald A. - Application 840159 (Reel 30, Frame 571)
      - Ho, David Da-i - Application 840160 (Reel 30, Frame 608)
      - Stanley, Samuel L., Jr. - Application 840161 (Reel 30, Frame 646)
      - Hearing, Patrick - Application 840162 (Reel 30, Frame 671)
      - Keene, Michael A. - Application 840163 (Reel 30, Frame 703)
      - Schlossman, David M. - Application 840164 (Reel 30, Frame 728)
      - Duguid, John R. - Application 840167 (Reel 30, Frame 758)
      - Grammas, Paula - Application 840169 (Reel 30, Frame 786)
      - Hewett, Kenneth W. - Application 840170 (Reel 30, Frame 814)
      - Luxon, Bruce A. - Application 840171 (Reel 30, Frame 844)
      - Berga, Sarah L. - Application 840172 (Reel 30, Frame 897)
      - Collier, Timothy J. - Application 840173 (Reel 30, Frame 937)
      - Schwarzenberg, Sarah J. - Application 840174 (Reel 30, Frame 969)
      - Van Dyke, Terri - Application 840175 (Reel 30, Frame 997)
      - McGonigle, Paul - Application 840176 (Reel 30, Frame 1032)
      - Natowicz, Marvin R. - Application 840177 (Reel 30, Frame 1065)
      - Hexem, John G. - Application 840178 (Reel 30, Frame 1097)
      - Schulkin, Jay - Application 840179 (Reel 30, Frame 1129)
      - Palker, Thomas J. - Application 840180 (Reel 30, Frame 1165)
      - Anderson, David J. - Application 840181 (Reel 30, Frame 1199)
      - Dills, Diana G. - Application 840182 (Reel 31, Frame 1)
      - Segal, Sharon A. - Application 840183 (Reel 31, Frame 37)
      - Wetzel, Daniel M. - Application 840184 (Reel 31, Frame 70)
      - Simasko, Steven M. - Application 840185 (Reel 31, Frame 93)
      - Clark, Michael - Application 840186 (Reel 31, Frame 126)
      - Kuljis, Rodrigo O. - Application 840187 (Reel 31, Frame 155)
      - Seeger, Chirstoph - Application 840189 (Reel 31, Frame 199)
      - Johnson, Alexander D. - Application 840190 (Reel 31, Frame 231)
      - Edwards, Robert H. - Application 840191 (Reel 31, Frame 260)
      - Weinberg, Richard J. - Application 840192 (Reel 31, Frame 288)
      - Ghosh, Debashis - Application 840194 (Reel 31, Frame 323)
      - Kirk, Kevin L. - Application 840195 (Reel 31, Frame 351)
      - Janik, John E. - Application 840196 (Reel 31, Frame 384)
      - Chu, Gilbert - Application 840197 (Reel 31, Frame 416)
      - Sharp, R. Mark - Application 840199 (Reel 31, Frame 445)
      - Idell, Steven - Application 840200 (Reel 31, Frame 474)
      - Widman, Lawrence E. - Application 840201 (Reel 31, Frame 507)
      - Uckun, Fatih M. - Application 840202 (Reel 31, Frame 539)
      - Nisen, Perry D. - Application 840203 (Reel 31, Frame 580)
      - Clark, Gregory A. - Application 840205 (Reel 31, Frame 616)
      - Seidlin, Mindell - Application 840206 (Reel 31, Frame 650)
      - Thummel, Carl S. - Application 840207 (Reel 31, Frame 679)
      - Rico, M. Joyce - Application 840208 (Reel 31, Frame 706)
      - Montelone, Beth A. - Application 840209 (Reel 31, Frame 735)
      - Leijten, Paul A. A. - Application 840210 (Reel 31, Frame 765)
      - Hannigan, Jerome J. - Application 840211 (Reel 31, Frame 792)
      - Chrysogelos, Susan A. - Application 840212 (Reel 31, Frame 820)
      - Manson, Nancy H. - Application 840213 (Reel 31, Frame 854)
      - Struhl, Gary - Application 840214 (Reel 31, Frame 878)
      - Arceci, Robert J. - Application 840215 (Reel 31, Frame 900)
      - Boom, Willem H. - Application 840216 (Reel 31, Frame 937)
      - Hageman, Gregory S. - Application 840218 (Reel 31, Frame 969)
      - Chiodini, Rodrick J. - Application 840219 (Reel 31, Frame 1019)
      - Getzoff, Elizabeth D. - Application 840220 (Reel 31, Frame 1053)
      - Davis, Roger J. - Application 840221 (Reel 31, Frame 1092)
      - Chervenak, Robert P. - Application 840222 (Reel 31, Frame 1129)
      - Leidy, John W., Jr. - Application 840223 (Reel 31, Frame 1160)
      - Erickson, Laurence A. - Application 840224 (Reel 31, Frame 1192)
      - Chen, Irvin, S. Y. - Application 840225 (Reel 32, Frame 1)
      - Simons, Robert W. - Application 840226 (Reel 32, Frame 31)
      - Barsky, Sanford H. - Application 840227 (Reel 32, Frame 61)
      - Braun, Jonathan - Application 840228 (Reel 32, Frame 91)
      - Abrams, Thomas W. - Application 850001 (Reel 32, Frame 156)
      - Cousin, Alan J. - Application 850002 (Reel 32, Frame 181)
      - Simard, J. Marc - Application 850003 (Reel 32, Frame 224)
      - Smith, Cheryl S. - Application 850005 (Reel 32, Frame 261)
      - Szczesna-Skorupa, Elzbieta - Application 850006 (Reel 32, Frame 297)
      - TSE, Doris Bo-Shan - Application 850007 (Reel 32, Frame 325)
      - Julius, David J. - Application 850008 (Reel 32, Frame 364)
      - Clark, Gregory A. - Application 850009 (Reel 32, Frame 394)
      - Myers, Alan M. - Application 850010 (Reel 32, Frame 427)
      - Hindenburg, Alexander - Application 850011 (Reel 32, Frame 458)
      - Shattuck, Karen E. - Application 850012 (Reel 32, Frame 492)
      - Rio, Donald C. - Application 850013 (Reel 32, Frame 528)
      - Kadonaga, James T. - Application 850014 (Reel 32, Frame 530)
      - Gibson, Kenneth M. - Application 850015 (Reel 32, Frame 560)
      - Misulis, Karl E. - Application 850016 (Reel 32, Frame 593)
      - Pardini, Bert J. - Application 850017 (Reel 32, Frame 623)
      - Moore, Steven A. - Application 850018 (Reel 32, Frame 655)
      - Warden, David A. - Application 850019 (Reel 32, Frame 694)
      - Gordon, Joel A. - Application 850020 (Reel 32, Frame 723)
      - Gordon, Ellen E. I. - Application 850021 (Reel 32, Frame 765)
      - Busa, William B. - Application 850022 (Reel 32, Frame 795)
      - Tait, Jonathan F. - Application 850023 (Reel 32, Frame 830)
      - Turker, Mitchell S. - Application 850024 (Reel 32, Frame 861)
      - Gardiner, Thomas W. - Application 850025 (Reel 32, Frame 888)
      - Smith, Mitchell R. - Application 850026 (Reel 32, Frame 931)
      - Emerson, Scott S. - Application 850027 (Reel 32, Frame 964)
      - Abdulwajid, A. D. - Application 850028 (Reel 32, Frame 993)
      - Henderson, Leslie P. - Application 850029 (Reel 32, Frame 1025)
      - Lybrand, Terry P. - Application 850030 (Reel 32, Frame 1057)
      - Robbins, David J. - Application 850031 (Reel 32, Frame 1087)
      - Dempsey, Walla L. - Application 850032 (Reel 32, Frame 1118)
      - Van Arsdell, Scott W. - Application 850034 (Reel 32, Frame 1153)
      - Badylak, Steven F. - Application 850035 (Reel 33, Frame 1)
      - Shrenker, Paul - Application 850036 (Reel 33, Frame 44)
      - Wile, Lawrence C. - Application 850037 (Reel 33, Frame 79)
      - Madl, James E. - Application 850038 (Reel 33, Frame 106)
      - Mais, Dale E. - Application 850039 (Reel 33, Frame 143)
      - Casella, Samuel J. - Application 850040 (Reel 33, Frame 185)
      - Kumar, M. K. Hari - Application 850042 (Reel 33, Frame 244)
      - LeBoeuf, Robert D. - Application 850043 (Reel 33, Frame 273)
      - Kujala, Gregory - Application 850044 (Reel 33, Frame 310)
      - Perentesis, John - Application 850045 (Reel 33, Frame 363)
      - Doillon, Charles J. - Application 850046 (Reel 33, Frame 401)
      - Caffrey, Martin - Application 850047 (Reel 33, Frame 430)
      - Simmons, Mark A. - Application 850048 (Reel 33, Frame 461)
      - Billadello, Joseph J. - Application 850049 (Reel 33, Frame 498)
      - Price, Ray M. - Application 850050 (Reel 33, Frame 527)
      - Sobotka, Paul A. - Application 850051 (Reel 33, Frame 561)
      - Cole, Gregory J. - Application 850052 (Reel 33, Frame 593)
      - Hartnell, Joan M. - Application 850053 (Reel 33, Frame 623)
      - Lash, Lawrence H. - Application 850054 (Reel 33, Frame 650)
      - Furdon, Paul J. - Application 850055 (Reel 33, Frame 681)
      - Bradshaw, Gary L. - Application 850056 (Reel 33, Frame 707)
      - Englund, Janet A. - Application 850057 (Reel 33, Frame 738)
      - Arslanian, Silva - Application 850058 (Reel 33, Frame 766)
      - Arnold, Frances H. - Application 850059 (Reel 33, Frame 799)
      - Ausubel, Kalman - Application 850060 (Reel 33, Frame 834)
      - Bearer, Elaine L. - Application 850062 (Reel 33, Frame 864)
      - Lustig, Robert H. - Application 850064 (Reel 33, Frame 901)
      - Nowicki, Stephen - Application 850065 (Reel 33, Frame 937)
      - Sudol, Marius - Application 850066 (Reel 33, Frame 970)
      - Koomey, John M. - Application 850068 (Reel 33, Frame 998)
      - Morcos, N. Charle - Application 850069 (Reel 33, Frame 1030)
      - Brookoff, Daniel - Application 850070 (Reel 33, Frame 1069)
      - Brenner, Daniel G. - Application 850071 (Reel 33, Frame 1104)
      - Carey, Jannette - Application 850072 (Reel 33, Frame 1137)
      - Margolskee, Robert F. - Application 850073 (Reel 33, Frame 1166)
      - Yaeger, Mark J. - Application 850074 (Reel 34, Frame 1)
      - Natowicz, Marvin - Application 850075 (Reel 34, Frame 42)
      - Poliakoff, Steven J. - Application 850077 (Reel 34, Frame 78)
      - Kilpatrick-Smith, Laurie - Application 850078 (Reel 34, Frame 109)
      - Landick, Robert C. - Application 850079 (Reel 34, Frame 145)
      - Molony, Jane L. - Application 850080 (Reel 34, Frame 184)
      - Buss, Janice E. - Application 850081 (Reel 34, Frame 215)
      - Buhle, E. Loren, Jr. - Application 850082 (Reel 34, Frame 246)
      - Kenney, Shannon - Application 850083 (Reel 34, Frame 284)
      - Kerdel, Francisco A. - Application 850085 (Reel 34, Frame 315)
      - Hempstead, Barbara L. - Application 850086 (Reel 34, Frame 348)
      - Wessale, Jerry L. - Application 850087 (Reel 34, Frame 381)
      - Roop, Roy M., II - Application 850088 (Reel 34, Frame 414)
      - Wong, Robert L. - Application 850089 (Reel 34, Frame 448)
      - Rhodes, David G. - Application 850090 (Reel 34, Frame 482)
      - Tamburini, Paul P. - Application 850091 (Reel 34, Frame 514)
      - Gordon, J. Bradley - Application 850092 (Reel 34, Frame 547)
      - Pantalos, George M. - Application 850093 (Reel 34, Frame 584)
      - Ballinger, Dennis G. - Application 850094 (Reel 34, Frame 615)
      - Tomiko, Sally A. - Application 850095 (Reel 34, Frame 645)
      - Howe, Christine L. - Application 850096 (Reel 34, Frame 675)
      - Celniker, Susan E. - Application 850097 (Reel 34, Frame 708)
      - Preston, Bradley D. - Application 850098 (Reel 34, Frame 737)
      - Hicks, David B. - Application 850099 (Reel 34, Frame 770)
      - Krikun, Graciela - Application 850100 (Reel 34, Frame 800)
      - Flomenberg, Phyllis R. - Application 850101 (Reel 34, Frame 832)
      - Kan, Chen-Chen - Application 850102 (Reel 34, Frame 865)
      - Gibson, Neil W. - Application 850103 (Reel 34, Frame 895)
      - Leyh, Thomas S. - Application 850104 (Reel 34, Frame 929)
      - Silver, Bernard J. - Application 850105 (Reel 34, Frame 960)
      - Wenger, Jay D. - Application 850106 (Reel 34, Frame 988)
      - Kaminski, Joanne M. K. - Application 850107 (Reel 34, Frame 1018)
      - Silver, Michael R. - Application 850108 (Reel 34, Frame 1051)
      - Powell, Saul R. - Application 850109 (Reel 34, Frame 1083)
      - Tausk, Francisco A. - Application 850110 (Reel 34, Frame 1113)
      - Ziegler, Steven F. - Application 850111 (Reel 34, Frame 1144)
      - Zeheb, Ron - Application 850112 (Reel 34, Frame 1174)
      - Leung, Kwanyee - Application 850113 (Reel 35, Frame 1)
      - Clark, John T. - Application 850114 (Reel 35, Frame 33)
      - Jackson-Cook, Colleen - Application 850115 (Reel 35, Frame 70)
      - Amatruda, Thomas T., III - Application 850116 (Reel 35, Frame 102)
      - Linz, John E. - Application 850117 (Reel 35, Frame 132)
      - Wilkinson, Miles - Application 850118 (Reel 35, Frame 163)
      - Clark, Michael T. - Application 850119 (Reel 35, Frame 196)
      - Brown, Laura J. - Application 850120 (Reel 35, Frame 226)
      - Wiest, Peter - Application 850121 (Reel 35, Frame 262)
      - Hutchins, Kenneth D. - Application 850122 (Reel 35, Frame 291)
      - Spain, James W. - Application 850123 (Reel 35, Frame 320)
      - Symington, Frank W. - Application 850124 (Reel 35, Frame 346)
      - Slade, Herbert B. - Application 850125 (Reel 35, Frame 377)
      - Yellen, Gary I. - Application 850126 (Reel 35, Frame 408)
      - Peterson, Christine - Application 850127 (Reel 35, Frame 437)
      - Houser, William H. - Application 850129 (Reel 35, Frame 478)
      - Hughes, Mark R. - Application 850130 (Reel 35, Frame 506)
      - Ravdin, Peter M. - Application 850131 (Reel 35, Frame 539)
      - Hobbs, Stuart F. - Application 850132 (Reel 35, Frame 570)
      - Rabkin, Samuel D. - Application 850133 (Reel 35, Frame 599)
      - Smalheiser, Neil R. - Application 850134 (Reel 35, Frame 630)
      - Grabowski, Paula J. - Application 850136 (Reel 35, Frame 667)
      - Weaver, David T. - Application 850137 (Reel 35, Frame 699)
      - Hoerr, Robert A. - Application 850138 (Reel 35, Frame 733)
      - Samuelson, John C. - Application 850139 (Reel 35, Frame 764)
      - Carras, Peter L. - Application 850140 (Reel 35, Frame 798)
      - Weiner, Francis R. - Application 850141 (Reel 35, Frame 825)
      - Langelan, Rosalie E. - Application 850142 (Reel 35, Frame 860)
      - Soltoff, Stephen P. - Application 850143 (Reel 35, Frame 884)
      - Shaw, George M. - Application 850144 (Reel 35, Frame 915)
      - Kawabata, Thomas T. - Application 850145 (Reel 35, Frame 957)
      - Hoenig, Margarethe - Application 850146 (Reel 35, Frame 1011)
      - Saad, Anuradha D. - Application 850147 (Reel 35, Frame 1045)
      - Landolfi, Nicholas F. - Application 850148 (Reel 35, Frame 1076)
      - Portnoy, Daniel A. - Application 850150 (Reel 35, Frame 1105)
      - Harris, David A. - Application 850151 (Reel 35, Frame 1141)
      - Dallas, Cham E. - Application 850152 (Reel 35, Frame 1171)
      - Fahih, M. Hasan - Application 850154 (Reel 36, Frame 1)
      - Porter, Mary E. - Application 850155 (Reel 36, Frame 23)
      - Kanki, Phyllis J. - Application 850156 (Reel 36, Frame 56)
      - Wu, Hen-Ming - Application 850159 (Reel 36, Frame 92)
      - Woychik, Richard P. - Application 850160 (Reel 36, Frame 125)
      - Koretsky, Alan P. - Application 850161 (Reel 36, Frame 151)
      - Spiro, Robert C. - Application 850162 (Reel 36, Frame 181)
      - Prussak, Charles E. - Application 850163 (Reel 36, Frame 217)
      - Buchmeier, Nancy A. - Application 850164 (Reel 36, Frame 249)
      - Calhoun, Jason H. - Application 850165 (Reel 36, Frame 279)
      - Carlton, Susan M. - Application 850166 (Reel 36, Frame 317)
      - Gundersen, Gregg G. - Application 850167 (Reel 36, Frame 349)
      - Redei, Eva - Application 850168 (Reel 36, Frame 385)
      - Mintzer, Jacobo E. - Application 850169 (Reel 36, Frame 426)
      - Melese, Teri - Application 850170 (Reel 36, Frame 461)
      - Palazzo, Robert E. - Application 850171 (Reel 36, Frame 492)
      - Kawamoto, Richard M. - Application 850172 (Reel 36, Frame 565)
      - Friedman, Richard A. - Application 850173 (Reel 36, Frame 595)
      - Putkey, John A. - Application 850174 (Reel 36, Frame 625)
      - Wray, Susan K. - Application 850175 (Reel 36, Frame 670)
      - Freeman, James W. - Application 850176 (Reel 36, Frame 704)
      - Surh, Linda C. - Application 850177 (Reel 36, Frame 734)
      - Marek, Kenneth - Application 850179 (Reel 36, Frame 769)
      - Jardieu, Paula M. - Application 850180 (Reel 36, Frame 800)
      - Livingston, David J. - Application 850181 (Reel 36, Frame 832)
      - Oester, Dean A. - Application 850182 (Reel 36, Frame 863)
      - Aronson, Frederick R. - Application 850183 (Reel 36, Frame 895)
      - Wolffe, Alan P. - Application 860001 (Reel 36, Frame 957)
      - Huerta, Michael F. - Application 860002 (Reel 36, Frame 987)
      - Mizisin, Andrew P. - Application 860004 (Reel 36, Frame 1025)
      - Brown, Scott A. - Application 860005 (Reel 36, Frame 1056)
      - Wilson, Raymond W. - Application 860006 (Reel 36, Frame 1089)
      - Garland, Theodore, Jr. - Application 860007 (Reel 36, Frame 1133)
      - Pollock, John A. - Application 860008 (Reel 36, Frame 1165)
      - Ballinger, Dennis G. - Application 860009 (Reel 36, Frame 1202)
      - Raghavan, Vigay K. - Application 860010 (Reel 37, Frame 1)
      - Palazzolo, Michael J. - Application 860012 (Reel 37, Frame 36)
      - Denning, Stephen M. - Application 860013 (Reel 37, Frame 65)
      - Stineman, Margaret G. - Application 860014 (Reel 37, Frame 94)
      - Zeichner, Steven L. - Application 860015 (Reel 37, Frame 132)
      - Hinrichs, Katin - Application 860016 (Reel 37, Frame 181)
      - Coutifaris, Christos - Application 860017 (Reel 37, Frame 213)
      - Butler, Patricia E. - Application 860018 (Reel 37, Frame 251)
      - Leibowitz, Mark D. - Application 860019 (Reel 37, Frame 282)
      - Greengard, Judith S. - Application 860020 (Reel 37, Frame 313)
      - Van Houten, Bennett - Application 860021 (Reel 37, Frame 344)
      - Yarnall, Michele S. - Application 860022 (Reel 37, Frame 379)